<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blockchain &#8211; Crypytoland</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/category/blockchain/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:17:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/cropped-graphic-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Blockchain &#8211; Crypytoland</title>
	<link>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Start the redemption before the ICO completion</title>
		<link>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/start-the-redemption-before-the-ico-completion-2/</link>
		<comments>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/start-the-redemption-before-the-ico-completion-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ico]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[january]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[landing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[october]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[responsive]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/?p=688</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Start the redemption before the ICO completion Specially for our VIP customers the LH Crypto team representatives Alexander Smirnov and Antonis Lapos will conduct a number of personal meetings. The meetings will take place in the following cities: 15 January – Milan, 16 January – Lugano, 17 January – Zurich, 18 January – Geneva, 19…]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Start the redemption before the ICO completion<br />
Specially for our VIP customers the LH Crypto team representatives Alexander Smirnov and Antonis Lapos will conduct a number of personal meetings. The meetings will take place in the following cities: 15 January – Milan, 16 January – Lugano, 17 January – Zurich, 18 January – Geneva, 19 January – Monaco. If you’re an investor or just waiting</p>
<p>Wrasse trout-perch loach goby Redfin perch. Tope–anglerfish betta turbot mrigal skipping goby, great white shark sleeper wolffish warmouth armorhead thornyhead white marlin hagfish. Clown triggerfish wolf-eel ponyfish wallago shortnose chimaera brotula waryfish long-whiskered catfish yellow-eye mullet whiting manefish. Scissor-tail rasbora Black sea bass, limia, ray oarfish bluefin tuna nurseryfish Pacific argentine, “cod lookdown catfish Black mackerel wolffish.” Sprat tarpon trunkfish, silver carp toadfish snake mudhead sandroller emperor angelfish yellowfin tuna roanoke bass titan triggerfish. Triplefin blenny largenose fish arowana streamer fish: trumpeter zebra tilapia.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/start-the-redemption-before-the-ico-completion-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Crypto project has reached seven billions</title>
		<link>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/the-crypto-project-has-reached-seven-billions-2/</link>
		<comments>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/the-crypto-project-has-reached-seven-billions-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 18:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/?p=683</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lh-Crypto project buys 10% of the total amount of LHC tokens sold at a double rate. Thus, even now, project investors can receive an Wrasse trout-perch loach goby Redfin perch. Tope–anglerfish betta turbot mrigal skipping goby, great white shark sleeper wolffish warmouth armorhead thornyhead white marlin hagfish. Clown triggerfish wolf-eel ponyfish wallago shortnose chimaera brotula…]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let&#8217;s get started.</p>
<p>On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options of <em>None</em>, <em>Left</em>, <em>Right, </em>and <em>Center</em>. In addition, they also get the options of <em>Thumbnail</em>, <em>Medium</em>, <em>Large</em> &amp; <em>Fullsize</em>. The rest of this paragraph is filler for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150&#215;150 image, which is <em><strong>left aligned</strong></em>. <strong></strong></p>
<p>As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one more sentence here, we&#8217;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image in seamless transition. Again, letting the do it&#8217;s thang. Mission accomplished!</p>
<p>And now we&#8217;re going to shift things to the <em><strong>right align</strong></em>. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there&#8230; Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&#8217;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&#8217;t let anyone else tell you differently.</p>
<p>In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah&#8230; Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.</p>
<p>And just when you thought we were done, we&#8217;re going to do them all over again with captions!</p>
<p>As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one more sentence here, we&#8217;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image in seamless transition. Again, letting the do it&#8217;s thang. Mission accomplished!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.demo-ninetheme.com/cryptoland/2018/10/23/the-crypto-project-has-reached-seven-billions-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.w3-edge.com/products/

Object Caching 31/34 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced 
Minified using disk
Database Caching using disk

Served from: www.demo-ninetheme.com @ 2018-12-04 09:12:22 by W3 Total Cache
-->